realjock.com 2007-11-13

# RealJock: Gay sports and gay fitness for gay jocks, athletes, and fitness buffs.

## PRIVACY POLICY

**INTRODUCTION**

We at RealJock, Inc., a California corporation ("RealJock") are firmly committed to protecting your personal information and informing you about how we handle it. Our goal of collecting this information is to provide you with the best possible experience at the RealJock Site located at www.realjock.com ("Website"). We have created this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to demonstrate our commitment to protecting your privacy and to inform you how the information you submit to us and the information that we collect automatically from you is handled. This Privacy Policy is intended to apply only to your transactions and activities, and the data gathered, on the Website. It is not intended to apply to any other website or offline point of contact between participants on the Website ("Participants") or any other companies or consumers. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may modify it from time to time. This Privacy Policy was last revised on October 10, 2005. Each time you visit the Website or provide us with information, by doing so you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy at that time.

**ELIGIBLITY**

**_YOU MUST BE AN INDIVIDUAL WHO IS AT LEAST EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OLD TO PARTICIPATE ON THE WEBSITE._**

You may not participate in the Website if you are under 18 years old. All adults are welcome to explore the Website and post a Profile; provided they comply with the Terms of Use. As per the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, any information input by minors will be purged from our database.

**OUR USE OF YOUR INFORMATION AND YOUR PROFILE**

RealJock collects a variety of information from you when you register with the Website, as well as during your use of the Website in order to provide you with best possible experience. None of the information collected by RealJock as part of the registration process is made accessible to the public, other users of the site, or anyone not employed by RealJock directly, except to the extent you include such information in your Profile (as defined in the Terms of Use) and to the extent that your age (not your date of birth) may be included by RealJock in your Profile. This information is held strictly confidential and can be deleted at the user's request. Nonmember visitors to RealJock are not allowed access to this information in any way.

Information you include on your Profile will be made accessible to other users of the site. This includes nonmembers who will be able to see your Profile if someone provides them with a direct link to your Profile (e.g. http://profile.realjock.com/membername). However, nonmembers will only see the primary image (non-adult), thumbnails of secondary non-adult images, and any text you have included about yourself. Of course, the nonmember will not be able to communicate with you without logging in.

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property; or (3) act in an emergency to protect someone's safety. In addition, as we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets and, depending on the transaction, your personally identifiable information may be one of the transferred assets. In the event that we are acquired by another company, your personal information may be part of the assets transferred to the acquiring party.

**INFORMATION YOU SUPPLY TO US AT REGISTRATION**

RealJock offers member and non-member based service to users. To process memberships and/or product purchases, we may require your name, age, billing address, phone number, email address, shipping address and credit card information. In general, you will receive one email notification confirming that you have created a membership, as well as one email notification every time you purchase a product or subscription from RealJock. You will be similarly notified of membership renewal transactions when they occur. If you have started, but not completed, the registration process, we may also send you email messages encouraging you to complete the process and become a subscriber. You will also be notified via email if you have new messages from other members on the Website, if you have been added to another member's hot lift or buddy list, or if a member you have added to your hot list or buddy list updates his or her Profile. You also have the ability to opt-in to receive emails about new products, promotions from RealJock or third-party partners of RealJock, although by default your Profile is set up not to receive those emails. You can change your preferences for the types of emails you receive from us in the Email preferences section of the Preferences tab, or by emailing us at [privacy@realjock.com](mailto:privacy@realjock.com). RealJock fully complies with the requirements of the federal CAN-SPAM ACT.

You may only access your Profile and personal information relating to you if you provide the correct password that you create when you register with the Website. After providing your password, you can edit or delete your information at any time.

If you forget your password, upon request we will email it to the email address you provide to us when you register. We will not give passwords out over the phone, nor will we email them to a different email address than the one used to register.

**INFORMATION WE AUTOMATICALLY COLLECT FROM YOU**

In addition to the information submitted by you, RealJock automatically collects certain information each time you visit the Website. For example, each time you visit the Website, RealJock will automatically collect your IP address, browser and computer type, access times, the web page from which you came and the specific Website pages accessed. If you choose to post messages in a forum, chat room or other message area, RealJock will only display such information about you as you choose to reveal.

Demographic and profile data is also collected by us through the Website. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our Website, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. Some of this information (e.g., customer demographic information) may be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We use cookies to collect this information and to deliver content specific to your interests, and if you so choose, to save other personal information so that you do not have to reenter it each time you visit the Website. If you wish to disable these cookies, the "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will give you instructions to do so. However, if you set your browser to disable or reject cookies, you will not be able to access the Website.

**YOUR PERSONAL CONTACT INFORMATION WILL NOT BE LENT OR SOLD TO ANY OTHER BUSINESS OR VENDOR.**

**PUBLIC FORUMS**

RealJock may offer in the future, message boards, calendars and other community tools that it will make available to its users and visitors. If so, please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personally identifying information.

**SECURITY**

RealJock has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. These measures include the use of Secure Server technology during credit card transactions and administrative access to site data, as well as other proprietary security measures which are applied to all repositories and transfers of user information. Although we will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure.

**HOW YOU CAN HELP PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION**

Do not disclose or share your login password with anyone. If you lose control of your login password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and will become subject to any legally binding action taken on your behalf. If your login password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.

Likewise, do not provide other account information, including your user name, to anyone. RealJock suggests that you not disclose personal, financial or address (home, business or hotel) information while using the Website or the Internet in general.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THIRD PARTIES**

On the Website, you may see links to other websites that are not owned by RealJock ("Unaffiliated Sites"). We do not control Unaffiliated Sites and this Privacy Policy does not apply to Unaffiliated Sites. When you click on these links and visit Unaffiliated Sites, the operators of the Unaffiliated Sites may collect different kinds of information about you and may use and disclose that information in different ways than we would if it were collected on RealJock's Website. In addition, third parties who place advertisements on the Website may also collect information through cookies to ensure that their advertising systems and technologies are functioning properly and to allow them to track your responses to their advertisements. Cookies set by these third parties are governed by the privacy policies set by the third parties. Since we are not responsible for the practices of third parties and Unaffiliated Sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any Unaffiliated Website or third party site with which you come in contact.

**CHANGING OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

If we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on the Website notifying users of the change. In some cases we will email users who have opted to receive communications from us where we post the Website notice, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

**ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY POLICY**

Your use of the Website, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this privacy statement and the Terms of Use that also govern your use of the Website. **BY USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR TERMS OF USE.** We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Your continued use of any portion of our Website following posting of the updated privacy statement will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact us:

By email: [privacy@realjock.com](mailto:privacy@realjock.com)

Copyright © 2006-2007 RealJock, Inc. All rights reserved
